// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: '"I\'m just slangin\' and bangin\'."', 
      a: 'West', 
      b: 'Molly',
      c: 'James',
      d: 'ChelsB',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: '"Did you know I was part of a gang called the Mouse Ball Bandits."', 
      a: 'Adam', 
      b: 'Billy',
      c: 'Taylor',
      d: 'Joelle',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: '"A lot of good pipe coming our way."', 
      a: 'Geoff', 
      b: 'RA',
      c: 'RG',
      d: 'Chris',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: '"I\'m so excited for assisted living, I can\'t even deal."', 
      a: 'Haley', 
      b: 'David J Neff',
      c: 'Cara',
      d: 'Couv',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: '"Wait, I\'m sorry... Are you eating that yogurt with a fork?? Can we talk about that first?"', 
      a: 'Kevin', 
      b: 'Devon',
      c: 'Marion',
      d: 'Jenn',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: '"I licked the shrimp."', 
      a: 'Lauren', 
      b: 'Jane',
      c: 'Nick R',
      d: 'Lynn',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: '"My life is a mess right now. Sometimes work gets in the way of my Slacking."', 
      a: 'JoCo', 
      b: 'Jalaliani',
      c: 'Catherine',
      d: 'Anjali',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: '"I can\'t quit you, Jane" ', 
      a: 'Phillip', 
      b: 'Juan',
      c: 'Dan',
      d: 'Libby',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: '"I stole undies..."', 
      a: 'Caitlin', 
      b: 'BDF',
      c: 'Devon',
      d: 'Marcus',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: '"I got bbq sauce in my cobbler slot!"', 
      a: 'Kendra', 
      b: 'Nick B',
      c: 'ChelseaN',
      d: 'Mitch',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};